Register of the Jacques Leprette papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- CD Data Discs, 1946-1995, undated
  - "Council of Europe,", 1949 (Box-folder 209: 7)
    One independently produced CD-ROM containing reports and other materials relating to the Consultative Assembly of the Council of Europe
  - "Paul M. G. Levy, le père spirituel du drapeau européen, le premier fonctionnaire européen,", 1950-1995 (Box-folder 209: 8)
    One independently produced CD-ROM containing materials about and by Paul M. G. Levy
- Oversize Materials, 1913-2004
  - Memorabilia, 1913-2004, undated
    - One plaque presented to Jacques Leprette by Major General E. A. Erskine, commander of the United Nations Interim Force in Lebanon (UNIFIL) (Box-folder 210: 1)
    - One German iron cross medal (Box-folder 210: 2)
    - One brooch with Nazi insignia (Box-folder 210: 3)
    - One compass (Box-folder 210: 4)
  - Posters, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 211: 1-102)
    One hundred two weekly posters produced by the Central Propaganda Office (Reichspropagandaleitung) of the German Nazi party (Nationalsozialistiche Deutsche Arbeiter Partei)
  - Serial issues
    - General, 1936-1969 (Box-folder 212: 1-51)
    - Newspapers published in French Algeria and containing articles about World War II, 1942 (Box-folder 213: 1-36)
    - Newspapers with articles about the Council of Europe, 1949 (Box-folder 213: 37-38)
    - Newspapers containing articles about the revolt of East German workers, 1953 (Box-folder 213: 39-53)
    - Newspapers with articles concerning the death of Joseph Stalin, 1954 (Box-folder 213: 54-64)
    - Newspaper with articles concerning the resignation of Richard Nixon, 1974 (Box-folder 213: 65)
- Draft of treaty establishing the Council of Europe, 1949 May 5